Update-channel acceptance against https://47.114.43.99.nip.io
Scratch install: C:\Users\Administrator\AppData\Local\Temp\sunday-update-verify
1. read the published manifest
  ok: manifest names a version (0.3.16)
  ok: manifest points at an https download (https://47.114.43.99.nip.io/downloads/Sunday_0.3.16_x64-setup.exe)
  ok: manifest carries a sha256
  ok: manifest carries a size (58231193 bytes)
2. download the installer and verify it like the app does
  downloaded 58231193 bytes, sha256 16bc6aaeb34d77002c9db8880b9b60d2ccd918af03e00d2e7342794e6e964c9a
  ok: downloaded size matches the manifest
  ok: downloaded bytes match the manifest digest
3. install it the way the in-app update does (silent + auto restart)
  ok: the installer exited 0 (got 0)
  ok: the installed application is in place
4. the setup must have started the application again
  ok: the application was started again by the setup (pid 36416)
  ok: the restarted application reports a healthy backend (port 49813)
Update-channel acceptance passed for 0.3.16
